[Music]
this mustn't register on an emotional
first distract target then block his
blind jab count with crossed 11 sheets
discombobulated dazed will attempt wild
haymaker employ elbow block and body
shot block feral left we can write draw
now fracture brick cracked ribs
traumatized Sullivan dislocate your
entirely you've kicked a diaphragm in
summary is ringing jaw fractured three
ribs cracked four broken diaphragm
hemorrhaging physical recovery six weeks
full psychological recovery six months
capacity dissipated back of head
utilized
[Music]
so it is difficult I I tried to obey but
killed him
kill him Tyrell now
[Music]
you're hurting me
Kendall I think you're having another
off day who the hell are you on our
future really my name is Chris listen I
think it's only fair that you pay for
the ladies breakfast no I feel really
like doodly when I'm with a dude
I mean then honestly when I have a dick
anywhere inside of me technically I
don't want to be technical about it now
I have a dick
[Applause]
[Music]
but you didn't say whether they knew you
borrowed it
do they know you borrowed it now hold o
these little booze meter mama
I'm Israeli and I hit the ball you wanna
let me call you back
lobbying is about foresight but
anticipating your opponents moves and
devising countermeasures
the winner plots one step ahead of the
opposition and plays her trump card
just after they play there's
you better not be saying that when
you're in there it's about making sure
you surprise them and they don't
surprise you the Ted Bundy story has
been recycled over and over and over
again it makes for a great entertainment
he's a fascinating evil character
it's a discounting of the stories of the
women in favour of the central hero
being the most important character in
the narrative and that is the failure to
look deeper and think harder about
violence against women in our culture
[Music]